[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the beginning of the new millennium, Russias, Iraqs and Saudi Arabias oil reserves were above 100 billion bbl.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Petite sizes are for women who are under 5 1.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The largest semilunar cartilages, also called the menisci, are located in this part of the body.", "correct_answer": "Knee", "incorrect_answers": ["Jaw", "Shoulder", "Hip"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Graduate, Elaine Robinson was engaged to another man when Benjamin Braddock proposed to her. What was his name?", "correct_answer": "Carl Smith", "incorrect_answers": ["Ben Billings", "Brian Avery", "Chuck Jones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What phobia is described as fear of marriage?", "correct_answer": "Gamophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Gynophobia", "Gephysrophobia", "Gerascophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of the following medications treats Alzheimers Disease (dementia)?", "correct_answer": "Aricept (donepezil)", "incorrect_answers": ["Topamax (topiramate)", "Effexor (venlafaxine)", "Lanoxin (digoxin)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Gollums real name before he became obsessed with the idea of having the One Ring?", "correct_answer": "Smeagol", "incorrect_answers": ["Smealum", "Gameagol", "Gamgee"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did Godzilla ever appear in a film with another famous Japanese movie monster called Gamera?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The success of Sylvester Stallone came with the blockbuster Rocky. He wrote the movie and also played the lead role. How many days did it take him to write Rocky?", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["26", "7", "48"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor starred as Captain Steven Hiller in the 1996 science fiction movie Independence Day?", "correct_answer": "Will Smith", "incorrect_answers": ["Martin Lawrence", "Chris Rock", "Cuba Gooding, Jr."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Rockys new protege in the movie Rocky Balboa?", "correct_answer": "Steps", "incorrect_answers": ["Tommy", "Rocko", "Billy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are twelve cranial nerves, two of which do not join the brainstem. Which are these two nerves?", "correct_answer": "olfactory and optical", "incorrect_answers": ["maxillary and mandibular", "vagus and accessory", "trigeminal and trochlear"]}]